Delmar Progress Club; Records mss148
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Delmar Progress Club Records
1902-2021, Undated
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
mss148
14.98 cubic ft.
The Delmar Progress Club Records document the day-to-day operations and communitiy activities of this Bethlehem-N.Y. based organization founded in 1901.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Delmar Progress Club donated all materials in this collection in November 2021.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is arranged into four series: administrative, events, publications, and subject files. The first three series are arranged chronologically, while the subject files series is arranged alphabetically.
Organizational Sketch
Established in 1901 in Delmar, N.Y., a hamlet in the town of Bethlehem, the Delmar Progress Club is a women's organization located in the Capital Region of New York State. The organization joined the New York State Federation of Women's Clubs in 1904, the General Federation of Women's Clubs in 1916, and was incorporated in 1929. The first president was Mrs. Sherman B. Rouse who served from 1901-1906.
The Delmar Progress Club was responsible for many community developments as the town of Bethlehem grew in the 20th century. In 1912, the Club raised money for books to establish the first free library in town and in 1913 organized the Delmar Free Library Association. The library was staffed and administered by Club volunteers for nearly two decades.
In addition, the Club named streets and numbered homes making the town eligible for mail delivery to residences. The Club's Civic Betterment committee petitioned the town to provide garbage collection, and it also is credited with leading the effort to establish the Town Planning Board.
Today the Delmar Progress Club remains active and engaged with the community and offers social and educational activities for its members.
Content Description
This collection contains administrative records including minutes, annual reports, by-laws, and a certificate of incorporation; membership lists, application materials, and club yearbooks (including calendar of events); club history and anniversary files; photo albums, photographs, and scrapbooks; multimedia items, i.e. CDs, DVDs, and VHS tapes; events and program files; financial records; publications; ephemera; and subject files.
Delmar Progress Club; Women--New York (State)--Societies and clubs; Minutes (administrative records); Financial Records; Women; Neighborhood and Community Associations; New York State Federation of Women's Clubs
- Administrative, 1902-2020, Undated; 1; 5.36 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the administrative records of the Delmar Progress Club, including meeting minutes, correspondence, financial documents, membership records, and committee reports. Meeting records comprise Bethlehem town board and school district meetings; Delmar Progress Club meetings, i.e. board of directors meetings, business meetings, executive board meetings, general meetings, past president's meetings, and special meetings; and General Federation of Women's Clubs (GFWC) meetings, i.e. bi-county meetings, mid-Hudson district meetings, third district meetings, and tri-county meetings. In the first few decades of the Club's existence, meeting roll calls were included with the meeting minutes. More recent Club meeting minutes are interfiled with agendas, ballots, by-laws and standing rules, citations, Club calendars, Club communications, correspondence, event invitations, financial documents, GFWC materials, member guidelines, lists of officer candidates and conference delegates, memoranda, motions, newspaper clippings, notes, policy documents, presentations, reports, resolutions, speech transcripts, webpages, and yearbooks. Meeting minutes are typically arranged by the fiscal year (October to May) rather than by calendar year. Correspondence is divided into general correspondence, which includes intra-Club and extra-Club communications, membership correspondence, and the papers of the Club's corresponding secretaries. Financial records include accounts, audit reports, bank books, checks, Club budgets and proposed budgets, GFWC finances, profit and loss standards, reports of the Club's treasurer, summaries, tax documents, and town budgets and tax reports. The early financial documents of the Club include lists of members, officers, and resignations. Membership records include address changes, applications for membership, dues paid, lists of members, lists of new members, lists of resignations, notices of the deaths of members, and reminders to contact members. Reports include the annual reports of the recording secretary, the corresponding secretary's reports, committee and group reports, conference reports, event reports, membership reports, New York Legislative Forum reports, the Club president's reports, school district meeting reports, task force reports, town board meeting reports, town planning reports, and the Club vice president's reports. This series also includes the Club's certificate of registry with the Home Education Department of the University of the State of New York, the Club constitution, the incorporation documents of the Club, various iterations of the Club's by-laws, scripts for the installation ceremony for new Club officers, rules for conducting meetings, parliamentary procedure guidelines, New York Legislative Forum by-laws and program schedules for 1974 and 1976, the notes of Club president Muriel H. Welch, and the personal notebook of Club President Wilma DeLucco. Finally, the series includes index cards, which include the member's name, her address, the date she joined, her Club identification number, the names of her sponsors, and the date she left the Club, for former Club members who have died or resigned.
  - Club Certificate of Registry with the University of the State of NY, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Club Roll Call and Meeting Minutes, 1903-1910; 1932 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Club Roll Call and Meeting Minutes, 1910-1914; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Club Roll Call and Meeting Minutes, 1914-1918; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Club Roll Call and Meeting Minutes, 1918-1919; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 1920-1923; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Club Roll Call, Meeting Minutes, and Reports, 1923-1929; 1936; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Club Old Typed Constitution and By-Laws, 1927; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Certificate of Incorporation of Club, 1929 (Flat-file 1, Folder 1)
  - Community Service Committee, Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1929-1930; 1989-1990; 1994-1995; 2011-2017; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 1929-1931; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Club Annual Reports, 1929-1931; 1933-1937; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Club Corporation Documents, 1929-1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Club By-Laws, 1929-2016; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Social Committee, Letter of Approval, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1931-1932; 1936; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Club Recording Secretary's Reports, 1931-1935; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Club Correspondence, 1932-1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Club Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1934; 1936-1937; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Club Secretary's Minutes, 1934-1937; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Club Financial and Membership Records, 1934-1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Club Budgets, Expenditures, and Tax Records, 1937; 1943-1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Club Executive Board and General Meeting Minutes, 1937-1939; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Club Bank Books and Records, 1937-1983; 1984-1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Club Financial Records and Membership Dues and Lists, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Club Secretary Reports and Meeting Minutes, 1939-1941; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Members Dues, 1940; 1943 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Club Budgets, Expenditures, and Tax Records, 1941-1943; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Club Annual Reports, Committee Reports, and Meeting Minutes, 1942-1943; 1955; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Club Secretary's Minutes, 1943-1945; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Club Financial Reports and Membership Records (Part 1 of 2), 1943-1950 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Club Financial Reports and Membership Records (Part 2 of 2), 1943-1950 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Club Secretary's Meeting Minutes, 1945-1947; Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Club Financial Records and Lists of Officers, 1945-1952; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Club Secretary's Minutes, 1949-1953; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports and Membership Dues and Lists, 1950-1955; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Club's 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1951; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Club Budgets and Receipts, 1952-1954; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Club Banking Records, 1953-1955; 1958; 1977; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 1953-1956; Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Club Membership Lists, 1953-1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Club Financial Reports and Membership Records, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Old Club Membership Lists with First Names and Addresses, 1954-1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Club Financial Records, 1954-1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Bethlehem/Delmar Public Library, 1957-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Club Membership Lists and Cards, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Club Accounts, Audit Reports, and Proposed Budgets, ca. 1962; 1997-2016; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Club Secretary's Minutes and Board of Directors Meetings, 1962-1964; 1967-1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Club Financial Reports and Membership Records, 1965-1970; 1975; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Index Cards, Club Members Who Died or Resigned, ca. 1965-2015 (Card-file 1)
  - Club Secretary's Reports and Meeting Minutes, 1970-1974; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Club Annual Reports and Business Meetings, Mrs. Dulle as Secretary (Part 1 of 2), 1971; 1974; 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Club Annual Reports and Business Meetings, Mrs. Dulle as Secretary (Part 2 of 2), 1971; 1974; 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Club Membership Lists, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Club Annual Reports and President's Reports, 1974-1976; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Club Annual Reports and President's Reports, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Reports (Part 1 of 2), 1977-1981; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Reports (Part 2 of 2), 1977-1981; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Club Membership Lists, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Club Financial Records, 1980-2000; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Corresponding Secretary's Notes, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Club Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1981-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Club Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1981-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Club Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1981-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Corresponding Secretary's Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Club Business Meetings, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Corresponding Secretary's Notes, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Club Annual Meeting Minutes, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Club General and Open Meeting Minutes, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Club Annual Reports, 1988-1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Club Report to General Federation of Women's Clubs Bi-County Meeting, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Parliamentary Procedure and Conducting a Regular Business Meeting, 1989; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Club Annual Meetings, 1989-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Club Board of Directors and Executive Board Meetings, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Club Membership Lists and Correspondence, 1990-1998; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Club Resolutions Committee, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Club Resolutions Committee, Joy Ford, 1991; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Club General Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Club Memberships Lists, 1992-1994; 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence Addressed to Lois Dillon, 1992; 2010-2012 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with Newspaper Clippings, 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Club Minutes and Annual Reports, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Club Minutes and Annual Reports, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Club President, Muriel H. Welch, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Membership, 1994-2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Club Minutes and Annual Reports, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Club Minutes, Reports, and Inventories, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, General and Papers, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Membership Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Club Nominating, 1998-2016; Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Club Resolutions Committee, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence General, 2000; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Corresponding Secretary Marian Choppy's Notebook, 2000-2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Club Treasurer's Reports and Other Financial Reports, 2000-2013; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Reports, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, General, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, General, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Reports, Ruth Navratil, Recording Secretary (Part 1 of 2), 2002-2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Reports, Ruth Navratil, Recording Secretary (Part 2 of 2), 2002-2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, General, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Club Expenses and Income, 2003-2013 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Annual Reports, Doris Kirk, Recording Secretary (Part 1 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Annual Reports, Doris Kirk, Recording Secretary (Part 2 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, General (Part 1 of 2), 2004-2006; Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, General (Part 2 of 2), 2004-2006; Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Club Meeting Minutes and Annual Reports, Doris Kirk, Recording Secretary, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, Margaret Gary (Part 1 of 2), 2006-2008; Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, Margaret Gary (Part 2 of 2), 2006-2008; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Membership Committee, 2006-2008; Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, New Club Members, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Resignations, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, General, 2006-2007; Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Corresponding Secretary, 2006-2010; 2012-2014; Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, New Club Members, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Resignations, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Received, 2007-2008; Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee, 2008-2010; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Received, 2008-2010; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Sent, 2008-2010; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2009-2010; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Club Committee and Study Group Reports, 2009; 2015-2017; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2010-2011; Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Membership Committee, 2010-2012; Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Attendance, 2010-2017 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2010-2012; Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2011-2012; Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Membership, 2011-2013; Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Membership Committee, 2012-2013; Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Corresponding Secretary, 2012-2014; Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Membership Committee, 2013-2014; Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Club President Wilma Delucco's Notebook, 2013-2017; Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2012-2014; Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Nonprofit Corporate Governance Guidelines and Policies, 2014; Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Membership Committee, 2014-2015; Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Conflict of Interest Policy and Certification Forms, 2014-2015; 2018-2020 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2014-2016; Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Corresponding Secretary, 2015-2016; Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs - New York State, Mid-Hudson District Reports, 2015-2017; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Membership Committee, 2015-2017; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, General, 2015-2018; Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Club Meeting Minutes (Part 1 of 2), 2016-2018; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Club Meeting Minutes (Part 2 of 2), 2016-2018; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Club Meeting Minutes, 2018-2020; Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Club Letterhead, Blank, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Club Commandments in 1918 Directory, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Club Membership Applications, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Club Membership Lists, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Club Officers, Installation Service, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Duties of Club President and Vice President, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Thank You Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Events, 1913-2021, Undated; 2; 1.45 cubic ft.
  This series contains records concerning events that the Delmar Progress Club organized and participated in, such as stage productions, Club annual or spring banquets, Club fall banquets, Club anniversary celebrations, Bethlehem Public Library anniversary celebrations, and charitable fundraisers. This series does not contain events organized by the General Federation of Women's Clubs or the New York State Federation of Women's Club; any materials relating to such events can be found in the subject files series. The materials in this series include event flyers, event booklets and programs, event calendars, song lyrics, newspaper clippings, dues statements, photographs, scripts for stage performances, request forms for event spaces, cast lists, correspondence concerning donations, sheet music, e-mails, Bethlehem Public Library newsletters, presentation scripts, history of the Delmar Progress Club, letters from the Club president, submissions to Progress in Print (the Club's newsletter) about upcoming Club events, photo albums for the Club's Festival of the Arts, and DVDs and VHS tapes. This series also contains records concerning the foundation, history, and upkeep of the Bethlehem Public Library, including history of the Bethlehem Public Library, meeting minutes from the Bethlehem Public Library Centennial Committee, the constitution of the Delmar Free Library Association, an annual report for the Delmar Free Library from 1914, and indentures from the will of George C. Adams to support the Delmar Free Library Association, and a resolution by the board of directors of the Delmar Progress Club to fund equipment and/or materials for the Bethlehem Library. Finally, the series contains the records of the Club's garden study group and the performing arts study group.
  - Bethlehem Public Library, Centennial Celebration, 1913-2013; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs Club Production, What Became of Parker, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Club Hosts Eleanor Roosevelt, 1930; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - George Washington Bicentennial Celebration, 1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Club Stage Productions, 1932-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual/Spring Club Banquet (Part 1 of 2), 1937-2019; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual/Spring Club Banquet (Part 2 of 2), 1937-2019; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Club's 110th Anniversary, The Way We Were/Are, 110 Years, 1937; 1959; 2001; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Concerts and Musical Events, 1944-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Club's Golden Jubilee, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Club Production of Lost in the Stars, 1959; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Bethlehem Public Library, 50th Anniversary, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Garden Group and Flower Show Programs, 1963-1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Club Sale to Aid Blind, ca. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fall Club Banquet, 1972-2017; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Club's Diamond Jubilee, 1974-1976; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Club's Diamond Jubilee, Large Ring in Metal Box, ca. 1974 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Club's Diamond Jubilee, Small Ring in Plastic Box, ca. 1974 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Holiday Tea, 1975-2012 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Members Dinner, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Best Times of Your Life Variety Show, ca. 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Club's 80th Anniversary Celebration, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Club's 85th Anniversary, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Delmar Progress Club, 85th Anniversary Show, 1987 May (Video-tape 1)
  - Bethlehem Public Library, Library Day, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Club Events, 1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bethleham Public Library, 75th Anniversary Celebration, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Literature Picnic, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, "...and Ladies of the Club" Luncheon, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photographs Removed from Photo Album, Festival of Arts, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photo Album, Festival of the Arts, 1990-1992; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Delmar Progress Club, Panel Discussion at Library, 1991 October 17 (Video-tape 2)
  - Progress Club, 90th Anniversary Dinner, 1991 October 22 (Video-tape 3)
  - Slides, Club's 90th Anniversary Banquet, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Club's 90th Anniversary Gala, 1991; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, Festival of The Arts, 1991; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, New Member Tea, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Club Productions of The Sitting, 1992; 1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Club Fashion Show, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Photo Album, Festival of the Arts, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - New York Federation of Women's Clubs, The Sitting, Saratoga, 1994 (Video-tape 4)
  - Progress Club Show, 1995 May (Video-tape 5)
  - Delmar Progress Club, 85th Anniversary Show, 1999 (Dvd 1)
  - Delmar Progress Club, 90th Anniversary Show, Rehearsal, 1999 (Dvd 2)
  - Delmar Progress Club, 90th Anniversary Show, 1999 (Dvd 3)
  - Delmar Progress Club, 95th Anniversary Fashion Show, 1999 (Dvd 4)
  - Delmar Progress Club, 100th Anniversary Show, 2000 November 10 (Dvd 5)
  - Delmar Progress Club, 100th Anniversary Show, 2000 November 10 (Video-tape 6)
  - Club's 100th Anniversary, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Performing Arts Group, A New York State of Mind, Club's 105th Anniversary, 2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Performing Arts Group, You Must Remember This, 2006; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Performing Arts Group, 2006; 2016-2019; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Performing Arts Group, A Very British Afternoon, 2008; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Bethlehem Memorial Day Parade, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Club Production of The Cape May Follies, 2009; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dollars for Scholars Card and Game Party, 2010; 2012-2013; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cheers for 85 Years, 2011 (Dvd 6)
  - Tulip Tea, 2011; 2013 (Box 3, Folder 5)